cindicator.com 2018-01-29

# 

                           Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy is designed to assist you with understanding how
Cindicator Limited, a private limited company organized under the laws
of Gibraltar (“Cindicator”, "we", "us" or "our") collect, use and disclose
the information you provide us when accessing or using the website,
www.cindicator.com.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
We may change this Privacy Policy in our sole discretion at any time. Any
revisions to this Privacy Policy will be posted on the homepage of our
Website. It is your obligation to periodically visit our Website to review
any changes that may be made to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use
of our Website constitutes your agreement to be bound by any such
changes to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy
Policy, you are not authorized to use our Website and your sole recourse
is to not use our Website.
What Information do we collect?
When you visit our Website, you may provide us with two types of
information: personal information that you voluntarily disclose that is
collected on an individual basis; and information collected automatically
when you use our Website or the services available on our Website
(collectively, the “Information”).
What is Personal Information?
Personal information is collected only when voluntarily offered and
solely for purposes that are clearly identified on our Website. Personal
information means any information that is unique to you, such as your:
      Full Name or the name of an entity you represent;
      Username Password, if required;
      Email address;
      Cryptocurrency address of your public Ethereum wallet address;
      Mailing address and country of residence;
      Proof of Address;
      Scan of your Personal ID;
      Other personal information you choose to provide such as your
         public LinkedIn account, your public Twitter account, your
         professional background, Cindicator’s products and services you
         might be interested in, your thoughts on how you can contribute
         to our Ecosystem.
By providing us with your personal information, you also consent for us
to collect, hold, use and disclose your personal information in
accordance with this Privacy Policy. In addition to providing the

foregoing information, if you choose to correspond further with us
through e-mail or through the “contact” section of our Website, we may
retain, use and disclose the content of your messages together with your
e-mail address and our responses.
What Information is Collected Automatically?
When you use our Website or services available on our Website, we
automatically collect information from your devices. We may collect the
following information:
     ●    Server Log Information: We collect server log information
          when you use our Website, which may include (but is not
          limited to) your login details, the date and time of visits, the
          pages viewed, your IP address, time spent at our Website and
          the websites you visit just before and just after our Website.
     ●    Device Information: We collect information about the computer
          or mobile device you use to access our Website, including the
          hardware model, operating system and version, the web
          browser you use, and other device identifiers.
     ●    Telemetry Information. If you use any of our open source
          software, we may collect bandwidth upload and download
          speeds, the amount of free and used storage space on your
          device and other statistics about your device.
     ●    Usage Information. If you use our Website, we will collect
          metadata about the files you upload for storage and we will
          record instances in which you have used your private key to
          authenticate communications.
     ●    Information Collected by Cookies and Other Tracking
          Technologies: We and our service providers use various
          technologies to collect information when you interact with our
          Website, including cookies and web beacons. Cookies are small
          data files that are stored on your device when you visit a
          website, which enable us to collect information about your
          device identifiers, IP address, web browsers used to access the
          Website, pages or features viewed, time spent on pages, mobile
          app performance and links clicked. Web beacons are graphic
          images that are placed on a website or in an email that is used
          to monitor the behavior of the user visiting the website or
          sending the email. They are often used in combination with
          cookies.
Use of Information
We will only use the Information for purposes of:
     ● providing, maintaining, delivering or improving our Website or
          the products or services provided through our Website;
     ●    verifying that you are a unique individual or entity;

     ●   conducting our white-listing process if you want to participate
         in CND token sale;
     ●   analyzing and tracking data to determine the usefulness or
         popularity of certain content and to better understand the
         online activity of our Website users;
     ●   fulfilling our legal or regulatory requirements;
     ●   providing you with the information or products or services that
         you have requested;
     ●   answering your inquiry or responding to a communication from
         you;
     ●   developing new products or services;
     ●   sending you technical notices, support or administrative
         notifications;
     ●   communicating with you about news, products, services, events
         and other information we think will be of interest to you;
     ●   matching your Information with job vacancies to assist us in
         finding a position that is most suitable for you if you have
         contacted us about recruitment;
     ●   monitoring and analyzing trends, usage and activities in
         connection with our Website;
     ●   detecting, investigating and preventing fraudulent transactions
         or unauthorized or illegal activities;
     ●   protecting the rights and property of the Cindicator Parties (as
         defined below) and others;
     ●   linking, connecting or combining Information we collect from
         or about you with other Information;
     ●   carrying out any other purpose or reason for which the
         Information was collected.
Sharing of Information
We will only share Information about you in the following ways:
     ● with your consent or at your instruction;
     ● with our current or future parent companies, affiliates,
         subsidiaries and with other companies under common control
         or ownership with us or our offices internationally;
     ● with third parties or service providers that perform work for us;
     ● certain information you may choose to share may be displayed
         publicly, such as your username and any content you post when
         you use interactive areas of our Website like our online forums;
     ● in connection with a merger or sale of our company assets, or if
         we do a financing or are involved in an acquisition or any other
         situation where Information may be disclosed or transferred as
         one of our business assets;
     ● in response to a request for information if we believe disclosure
         is in accordance with, or required by, any applicable law,
         regulation or legal process;
     ● if we believe your actions are inconsistent with our user

         agreements or policies, or to protect the rights, property and
         safety of any Crypto. Tickets Party or others;
     ●   with third parties where aggregate Information is disclosed
         which cannot be reasonably be used to identify you.
Social Sharing Features
Our Website may offer social sharing features, links to social media and
other integrated tools. Your use of such features enables the sharing of
information with your contacts or the public, depending on the settings
you use with the entity that provides the social sharing feature or social
media. Please visit the privacy policies of the entities that provide these
features to obtain more information about the purpose and scope of data
collection and the processing of such data by such entities.
Protection of Personal Information
We take reasonable steps to protect the security of the information
communicated through our Website. However, no computer security
system is entirely foolproof and the Internet is not a secure method of
transmitting information. As a result, we do not assume any
responsibility for the data you submit to or receive from us through the
Internet or for any unauthorized access or use of that information and
we cannot and do not guarantee that information communicated by you
to us or sent to you by us will be received or that it will not be altered
before or after its transmission to us. You agree to not hold us and our
respective past, present and future employees, officers, directors,
contractors, consultants, equity holders, suppliers, vendors, service
providers, parent companies, subsidiaries, affiliates, agents,
representatives, predecessors, successors and assigns (collectively, the
“Cindicator Parties”) liable for any loss or damage of any sort
incurred as a result of any misappropriation, interception,
modification, deletion, destruction or use of information provided
through our Website.
Most web browsers are set to accept cookies as a default. You may wish
to opt out by turning off cookies (please refer to the help menu on your
browser); however, switching off cookies may restrict your use of our
Website.
You may also opt out of receiving promotional communications from us
at any time by following the instructions in those communications. If you
opt out, we may still send you non-promotional communications, such
as technical notices, support or administrative notifications or
information about your account (if you have one).

Hyperlinks and Third-Party Sites
This Website may contain links to other third party websites that may
collect personal information about you, including through cookies or
other technologies. If you link to another website, you will leave this
Website and this Privacy Policy will not apply to your use of and activity
on those other websites. You should consult these other websites'
privacy policies as we have no control over them and are not responsible
for any information that is submitted to or collected by these third
parties.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us
at support@cindicator.com.
Dated: September 7, 2017
